

Having 5 + Years Of Experience on Microsoft Dot Net Technologies And Completed B.Tech In Information Technology in JNTU Hyderabad.



Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 2 Month(s)

Pref. Location: Hyderabad Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming / Highest Degree: M.Tech [Computers]

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: c#.net, asp.net, mvc, ,sql server, entity framework, ado.net, javascript, ajax

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Summary

Having 5.3+ Experience Dot Net Technologies, Worked As A Senior Software Engineer in Prime Ki Software Solutions from Feb 2019 to August 2020 and

Worked As a Senior Software Engineer in Cyient Ltd from

from Dec 2017 to 29 Jan 2019.

And Worked As a Software Engineer at Creative App Studios from Sep 2015 to Sep 2016 and Worked As a Software Programmer at Coign Edu & It Services Pvt Ltd from March- 2014 to Aug- 2015

Work Experience

Prime Ki Software Solutions (Prime Technology Group LLC) as Senior Software Engineer Feb 2019 to Aug 2020

Worked As a Senior Software Engineer in Prime KI Software Solutions Pvt Ltd. and my Rolls and Responsibility to Gathering Information from My team Leader and Analyse the Task and Implementing in Code Level , Writing Stored Procedures and Creating Tables.

Cyient Ltd, Hyderabad as Senior Software Engineer Dec 2017 to Jan 2019

Worked As a Senior Software Engineer in Cyient Ltd. and my Rolls and Responsibility to Gathering Information from My team Leader and Analyse the Task and Implementing in Code Level, Writing Stored Procedures and Creating Tables.

Creative App Studios as Software Engineer Sep 2015 to Sep 2016

Worked As a Software Engineer in Creative App Studios and my Rolls and Responsibility to Gathering Information from My team Leader and Analyse the Task and Implementing in Code Level, Writing Stored Procedures and Creating Tables

Coign Edu & It Services Pvt Ltd as Software Programmer.

Mar 2014 to Aug 2015

Worked As a Software Programmer in Coign Edu & It Services Pvt Ltd. and my Rolls and Responsibility to Gathering Information from My team Leader and Analyse the Task and Implementing in Code Level and Creating Tables

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University (JNTU) Hyderabad in 2012

PG: M.Tech (Computers) in 0

IT Skills

| Skill Name | Version | Last Used | Experience |
|------------|---------|-----------|----------------------|
| C#.NET | 4.5 | 2020 | 5 Year(s) 0 Month(s) |
| MVC | 5.0 | 2020 | 5 Year(s) 0 Month(s) |
| SQL Server | 2008 | 2020 | 5 Year(s) 0 Month(s) |

Languages Known

| Language | Proficiency | Read | Write | Speak |
|----------|-------------|------|-------|-------|
| English | Proficient | | | |
| Telugu | Proficient | | | |
| Hindi | Proficient | | | |

Affirmative Action

Category: OBC - Creamy

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Countries: India

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time